<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide App</string>

    <string name="murree_tour_guide_app">Murree Tour Guide App</string>
    <string name="enter">Enter Tour</string>

    <string name="hotel">Hotels</string>
    <string name="park">Parks</string>
    <string name="hill">Hills</string>
    <string name="restaurant">Restaurants</string>

    <string name="maisonette_fir_hill">We at Firhill Villas Murree understand that good food is an important element in making your stay with us a memorable one. Along with a twenty four hour room service and a chef-on-call, you can enjoy eating indoors or out on the terraces by food prepared to the highest standards. \n\nThe choices available are varied ranging from Continental, Chinese to our timeless Desi classics with a live kitchen where you can enjoy a fresh and succulent BBQ dinner. Chef Niazi who heads our kitchens, has worked extensively in the food industry in Pakistan and abroad. \n\nOur Food division is a largely operating set of restaurants, serving 30000+ guests per year. We work closely with our restaurant concept departments to develop the best food taste and service. These solutions deliver unique, award-winning concepts that are guaranteed to provide guests with exceptional experiences. So when your guests sit down to enjoy a meal, it\'s a memorable experience. \n\nWorld-class food is the hallmakr of Firhill Villas and is exemplified by distinguished dining. Our ever extending menu includes Pizzas, Burgers, Sandwiches, Soups, Chinese, Salads, Steaks, BarBQ and Fish.</string>
    <string name="punjab_huts">Located right on the main Bhurban road and spread over kanals of serene estate, Punjab Huts Resort is certainly a prime holiday destination for travellers who know and appreciate the very best. Managed by the seasoned hoteliers, it is an ideal retreat for those who want an upscale and high-end living away from the crowds yet at a close distance from key landmarks of the area e.g. Mall Road, PC Bhurban, Patriata, Ayubia etc. \n\nOur Delux Rooms have a separate balcony whereas each Suite has its own private terrace giving breathtaking views of Kashmir Hills and Bhurban Valley.</string>
    <string name="morning_side_murree">34 Morning Side is a newly established resort located in posh Kashmir Point area in Murree, Punjab, Pakistan. It\'s situated in one of the oldest British hill-stations. It\'s a 2 star hotel which make your stay as memorable as possible. 34 Morning Side all 14 Suites have been equipped with these facilities including central heating system, 32 inch television with cable connection, internet access with more than 3000 Songs available on the computer in each suite. They give you a warm and friendly environment and provide good services. 34 Morning Side all suites are well decorated with distinctive style and beautiful furnished classic furniture. You will definitely enjoy your tour with us at Murree Hills.</string>
    <string name="faran_hotel">We treat Customer Relation as a strategic business issue, and an integral part of our vision to become one of the most professionals in the hospitality industry. As our approach to Customer Care is always believing in going an extra mile to serve our Guests. We have reopened our doors after a complete refurbishing of the hotel. We believe that striving to take an industry lead and making Customer Care a genuine part of our overall strategy to create standard hotels that our guests trust and always prefer will enable us to serve them better, we do our utmost in making our valued guest feel at home. Faran hotel has a truly unique view of the exciting urban tradition from the spacious and luxurious guestrooms, and its various state of the art facilities. At this amazing one and only location, we provide our guests, top class lodging, full blown convention facility and service, wedding services, and most importantly a refined and sincere hospitality. The perfect setting for your dream Wedding. The venue provide a beautiful backdrop for wedding photography and reception. As dusk falls gardens, the pathways are romantically lit, giving that extra special ambience to the day. \n\nWe ensure that you will have our full attention and assistance with all of your catering requirements, and offer professional advice where needed. We know that flexibility for your most important day is key. We have our own in-house event organisers, to make sure that you have a beautiful and memorable day. We make every effort to make that day, the best day of your life. The setting you choose for your wedding day can transform a special day, to an extra special day. We understand that every couple has a different budget and we hope to have something to suit them all. We now offer flexibility on our prices, so please come and meet our Events Coordinator to talk you through the best options for your budget. Our greatest strength is the ability to deliver a top quality product. After numerous years in the business we understand how best we serve our valued guests to the best of their satisfaction.</string>
    <string name="bhurban_hills">Bhurban Hill Apartments offer easy access to Murree if you want to enjoy snowfall or thinking to explore the natural beauty of Murree and its surrounding areas. It is an escape from Pakistan\'s hot temperatures during summer and school holidays. Bhurban Hill Apartments are surrounded by pine trees in a quiet environment in Bhurban, away from noise and congestion. Our apartments are the best choice if you plan to stay away from the crowd of Murree but have easy access to the main sites of Murree including Mall Road, Kashmir Point, Gilliat, Nathia Gali, Ayubia, Patriata, Kohala bridge, Golf Course and PC Bhurban. \n\nBy staying with us you will experience a luxurious, unique and comfortable stay in Murree, be it  for leisure or business purposes. It is an enclosed compound with secured parking, boundary wall, fence and guard ensuring the safety of our guests. You will also appreciate our family-friendly approach, space and privacy we offer when travelling with children. </string>
    <string name="red_himalayans">Hotel Red Himalayan is best budget family hotel near Mall road Murree at Jhika Gali Road. Hotel Red Himalayan is located in the heart of Murree the beautiful Hill Station of Pakistan. Hotel Red Himalayan is a fabulous hotel in Murree with 42 rooms including Standard and Executive Bedroom. Each of them is well equipped with modern amenities and excellent services. Your stay includes FREE WiFi, 24 hours room service, Telephone, Cable TV, facility is also available at hotel. The hotel, with beautiful architecture, provides stunning view of the mountains, natural beauties and beautiful walks away from the mall.</string>
    <string name="bright_land_hotel">Brightlands Hotel is located close to Mall road in Murree, Pakistan. The hotel boasts a 24-hour electricity and offers free WiFi to all guests. \n\nAll the rooms Brightlands Hotel spacious and have air conditioners installed, a mini-sitting area, a fan , a telephone, a TV set and designed with an en-suite bathroom. \n\nBreakfast, lunch and dinner is served daily for a surcharge. The onsite restaurant serve variety of meals to guests and visitors. \n\nBrightlands further facilitates the guests with laundry and car hire services for extra charge. Onsite parking is available and the premises are guarded by security personnel. \n\nBrightlands Hotel is at a 7-minute drive from Mall Road and 1 km away from the Public Transport.</string>

    <string name="lake_view_park">Lake View Park (also called Rawal Lake Park) is situated on Murree-Islamabad Highway. While traveling from Islamabad to Murree a road turns right just before Barakahu and leads to this beautiful park. The newly constructed park has become a favorite picnic spot for people of Islamabad and Rawalpindi. It  is constructed alongside Rawal Lake, which is an artificial reservoir that fulfills water needs for cities of Rawalpindi and Islamabad. \n\nCDA has displayed list for almost all the fun activity and amusements available in the park. Parking is very vast and inexpensive. The place is also very good for bird lovers as the majority of birds of Islamabad and Rawalpindi can be found here. Lake View Park can also be reached using public transport. Vans of root No. 10 from Rawalpindi and root No. 127 from Islamabad can be used to reach this park.</string>
    <string name="chattar_park">The Chattar water park is only 15 minutes outside Islamabad. There is also an alternate but longer route to Murree from Islamabad via Nilore and Simli Dam. The alternate route joins at Lower Topa. The mountain drive is refreshing and the scenery is breath-taking especially on the Nilore-Simli-Lower Topa route. \n\nThis resort nestles at the base of Murree hills at a distance of 15 km on Islamabad-Murree road. This place offers scenic walks, gently flowing stream, waterfall and the surrounding hillside are a perfect attraction. The resort has a restaurant, barbecue and two air-conditioned tourist cottages. The Children\'s Park and playground are spread over an area of 12.5 acres.</string>
    <string name="sozo_adventure_park">Located on the main canal road near Jallo, Sozo Water Park covers a total area of 25 acres and is home to some of the most action-packed, adrenaline-pumping and exhilarating water slides and dry rides. \n\nSozo is the Greek word for Salvation. Sozo Water Park is salvation from the intense summer heat of Lahore for all those who are looking to treat themselves to extreme fun, refueling and excitement.\n\nSozo Water Park is managed by experienced and reputed team of individuals who take pride in being the pioneers in bringing water-based craze and recreation for the people of Pakistan. \n\nAll the rides are individually checked and certified by the engineers of University of Engineering and Technology (UET), Lahore to make sure everyone who comes to Sozo Water Park is safe and secure during their extraordinary day out. Any ride and/or slide is not operated without a certificate from UET. \n\nThe water park has a standalone water filtration and chemical treatment to make sure the people play in safe and clean environment free from dirt and germs.\n\nThe place is teeming with lifeguards and security guards who make sure everyone stays safe. \n\nSo, come on… Visit Sozo Water Park with your friends and family today for an unforgettable, seemingly never ending journey of fun and play time. </string>
    <string name="valley_park">Valley Park is Best place in summer as well as in the winter to enjoy, basically it is a stopover point you may not find any hotel to stay here. TDCP or the Tourism Development Corporation of Punjab is a tourism promoter in Punjab province, has a hotel on this spot for tourists and visitors. TDCP Hotel Salgran offers almost all types of Pakistan and Chinese foods. It covers a small area and provides facilities to the visitors. It is situated on the opposite side of the Valley Park Salgran.\n\nAs getting into Valley Park you could see many attractions in it for the families and children. It truly is a heaven for children and families, attractions for kids are there along the food. A huge parks place is also there for cars and buses etc. \n\nYou could enjoy hills, park and water stream on the same location of Valley Park or Salgran Park. Above are the mountains and below is the water stream, it make and complete the beautiful scene of this place which attracts the people to itself.</string>
    <string name="murree_wildlife_park">Murree Wildlife Park is a Zoo located in Bansra Gali, in Murree Pakistan. This Park was initially inaugurated under the National Development Scheme \'Development of Wildlife Park\' n 1986. The wildlife park provides canteens and cafeterias for the tourists and visitors. The Murree Wildlife Park covers an area of 240 acres. The wildlife park has Asian black bear, Bactrian camel, Chital, Chinkara and Sambar.</string>
    <string name="pia_park">PIA park is different from the rest of murree, its open and quiet place on height, and one can enjoy scenery of mountains and weather while sitting with family. The park provides canteens and cafeterias for the tourists and visitors and is the best place in summer as well as in the winter to enjoy.</string>

    <string name="changla_gali">Changla Gali is a hill station located in the Galiyat, are which borders NWFP and Punjab, starting at Murree and ending at Thandiani. About two miles further up and nine miles/14 kms. from Murree, on the main Abbottabad-Murree road, is Changla Gali, splendidly situated at an altitude of 8,400 f / 2560m amidst thick pine forest. The 9,000 f / 2743 m. Changle peak commands, on the one side a fine view of the Jhelum Valley, on the other side it presents a strikingly panoramic of the Murree hills, the southern portion of the Hazara district and the distant plains of Rawalpindi.\n\nChanglagali is the highest point in the Murree Galliat area which is accessible by road. There is a rest house located in the most picturesque surroundings. A number of good hotels and restaurants are available at the spot. Changla Gali is one of the smaller resorts, most people preferring to stay at either Nathiagali or Murree.\n\nNatural springs abound Changlagali on the slopes and their water is stored in reservoirs to provide water supply for Murree and adjoining areas.</string>
    <string name="ghora_daka">The Ghora Gali (elevation 5,000 ft), known as such because this place was used for the changing of horses used for carriages operating between Rawalpindi-Murree and further on to Srinagar (Kashmir) during the British period. TDCP construct a restaurant in-between the natural sceneries for tourist. The snake bar and all other facilities are available here.</string>
    <string name="kalabagh_point">A little up from Nathia Gali bazar, at the top of the hill is situated "Green Spot". Actually this is a Pakistan Air Force reserved area, but it is open for tourists and families. You can enter Green Spot by paying Rs. 5/- as entrance fee. View of Nathiagali and neighbouring area is magnificent from here.</string>
    <string name="kashmir_point">Leave Mall road from other end, going up GPO and walk for fifteen minutes, about 1 km it will leads to Kashmir point. You may hike up to the Kashmir point. The way passing by the Cadet College Murree goes towards the Murree Residence of the President of Pakistan. \n\nIt has a beautiful sight seeing. You can see Kashmir mountains from this point. It is the highest spot in Murree and due to increasing rush on Mall road, this point is taking visitor’s attention day by day. \n\nNow it has a long bazaar, a joy land and lots of eating places. Most of the visitors came to ease down and relax in Murree and need a quite place to live so they prefer to book a room in Kashmir point instead of Mall road.</string>
    <string name="mushpuri_top">Mushkpuri Hill, the second highest hill in Galiyat, above 9,000 feet sea level. This may be one of the closest places where you can gain such height. Starting from Pines Hotel NathiaGali or Dewan House DungaGali, the trek passes upward through lush green forests. Beautiful Daisies dance and swing to greet the hiker and sets the romantic charm, specially in the rainy weather with hide and seek of the scenery is all around you.</string>
    <string name="patriata_new_murree">Patriata is about 15 kilometer away from main Murree hills on the Lower Topa side. It is a well developed hill station with great high rised trees, beautiful hills.\n\nThis is famous due to chair lift, which worth a ride. A world class chair lift and cable car system takes you from New Murree to Patriata. Total ride is about 7 km long. New Murree is on ground level between the hills. Here you have to buy the ticket for Chair Lift + Cable Car which is Rs. 200/- then a chair lift ride takes you to a middle hill. You can watch Kashmir mountains from middle Hill where Chair Lift takes you. You may stay here for some time and enjoy Tea/Coffee or just walk around. From there Cable car takes you to Patriata Hill. where you have much stuff to do. Walk freely everywhere. Just walk in the direction where most of the tourists are going. Straight road takes you to the highest point of the hill. Where scenary is panoramic. On one side you can watch Murree Hills and on the other side snow covered Kashmir Hills.\n\nThe Chair Lift and Cable Car journey is memorable of life time. You can witness lots of great scenaries of near and far hills. In winter all hills are covered with snow while in summer lush green scenarios could be seen.\n\nYou may ride a horse but ASK/FIX CHARGES before leaving otherwise they will charge you too much. Similary don\'t hire a guide within patriata. People will come around you like they are helping you in taking pictures but then they ask huge amount for those services.\n\nPrivate car from Murree charges about Rs. 800/- for return journey. Driver will leave you at the gate of TDCP PATRIATA RESORT at New Murree and then take you back to Murree when you\'ve finished.\n\nYou can\'’t stay there for long. Last cable car is at 5 pm which take every visitor back. At that time a person goes all the way whistling to check if there is any one left and then take last cable car.</string>
    <string name="pindi_point">Pindi point is one of the prime points to visit in Murree. It is 15 minutes walk from mall road. It has a beautiful view of vallies and mountains. You can see Pindi city from there. Chairlift rides go down 1.5 km from Pindi Point to Bansara Gali are really enjoyable. Scenary from chair lift is magnificent. Zigzag road passes below. Great pine trees stand throughout the journey. When go down the valley there is a stop point. You can enjoy a lot there. There is a coffee shop and children play land. Hills of Patriata can be seen there. A great jungle starts there. You can enjoy tracking. Chair lift is open from 9am till 6 pm.</string>

    <string name="alpine_hangout">Alpine Hangout offers you the most happening place in the scenic environments of Murree, which delight and indulge the senses. Located on Jinnah Road, Murree Cantonment, near Combined Military Hospital (CMH), is a wonderful place to let loose, let the good times roll and share a memorable experience with family, friends or colleagues in the culinary world of a thousand flavours. With a desire to introduce cutting edge Western, Chinese, Pakistani, Barbecue and Grilling, Fast Food Cuisine and Bakery Products. Alpine Hangout offers you the best restaurant services, where one will find quality food prepared under the supervision of splendid chefs duly served by equally courteous staff. Fresh and exciting menu covering large variety of food at affordable rates, adding to your cherishing memories of visit. Rest assure, our efficient management will take full care of you and your dear ones, in all kinds of weather extending complete family privacy. Embrace the warm and friendly service that offers a truly unpretentious, genuine and incredibly rich dining experience.</string>
    <string name="hilltop_resort_khajut">TDCP Hilltop Resort Khajut is 27 km from phulgaran toll plaza barakahu on expessway from islamabad to murree, Murree, Pakistan-051, it is the place where you can enjoy the natural beauty.\n\nThe resort built on the beautiful hills of Murree...The place where you can enjoy lahori taste of food,best room services,camping and tourism services. \n\nBarbeque, Breakfast, Brunch, Burgers, Chinese, Fast Food, French, Indian/Pakistani, Sandwiches, Seafood, Steakhouses and Vegetarian. \n\n\Public transport is the easy way to reach the resort.27 k.m from Bharakahu (on expressway from Islamabad to Murree).Khajut Near Murree\n\n akes Reservations, Walk-Ins Welcome, Good For Groups, Good For Kids, Take Out, Waiter Service and Outdoor Seating</string>
    <string name="lintott_restaurant">A little up from Nathia Gali bazar, at the top of the hill is situated "Green Spot". Actually this is a Pakistan Air Force reserved area, but it is open for tourists and families. You can enter Green Spot by paying Rs. 5/- as entrance fee. View of Nathiagali and neighbouring area is magnificent from here.</string>
    <string name="red_onion">Red Onion offer variety of different cuisines, which are of great quality and taste. Environment is superb and their specialty is lots of variety on their menu.</string>
    <string name="white_union">White Onion offer variety of different cuisines, which are of great quality and taste. Environment is superb and their specialty is lots of variety on their menu.</string>

</resources>
